So today we have Akari Yoshida with us!
Hello everyone, my name is Akari Yoshida, aka Akarin.
I'm Akarin Yoshida, a.k.a. Akarin Yoshida.
Akarin
I've been a member of NMB for a year.
I was also a member of NMB for a year.
That's right.
We're on the same team.
Yes, the same team.
We went on tour together, right?
Akari is the one who helped me the most in NMB.
I've said this in many places.
That's not true.
I was also a starter for AKB, so I was very supportive.
It was reassuring to know that there was someone who knew me.
But maybe if we only watched each other's YouTube videos...
I don't know what kind of people were involved with Roof.
I don't know if there are people who don't know who I was related to at Roof.
In this video, I show you
This is the one cosmetic that I can't give up.
I'd like to do a little something like that.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
I'm going to ask a few questions and go over a few things.
First of all, the base.
Recently, I've been using two primers.
Or one?
I'd like to know which one you recommend.
This one.
It's COSME DECORTE's Sun Shelter Multi-Protection Tone-Up CC No. 10.
It's a sunscreen emulsion and a makeup primer in one.
Sounds good.
Exquisite.
I love it.Don't you?
I love pink.
Isn't it great?
I love it so much.
It's a little too red.
It's very pink, but it adds a little bit of blood color.
But it's so clear and even.
It's the pink I was really looking for but didn't find it.
All face?
I'm going for the whole face.
I'll buy it.
Please buy it.
I'm sure you know what I'm talking about.
Shibashi blue.
A little bit on the cheeks and dark circles.
To make it transparent.
I also use green and orange.
I use blue most of all.
I also use blue and green a lot.
Green also has a reddish tint.
I'd like to introduce you to just a little bit of foundation.
It's Lior's Prestige White Loop Protector UV Mineral BB.
White Loop Protector UV Mineral BB
Once you use it, you'll never go back!
Seriously?
I really can't go back!
I'm wearing it today.
It's been this shiny all the time.
It's so beautiful!
If you're looking for a lot of coverage, maybe it's not enough.
You may feel it's not enough.
But you can't get the same kind of shine with this.
I thought so much about it.
I wondered why they were doing that when I came in.
Really?
It's almost 15,000 yen, and they keep raising the price.
That's right.
The price of the foundation...
The price of foundation is directly related to the quality of the product.
That's right.
It's really worth it.
I see.
I want you to try this.
This is the foundation I've been using lately.
It's really good.
It's great.
The one you gave me.
It's so good.
It's amazing.
I'm just saying, it's not like it's Depakos or anything.
But the shine, the coverage, the color.
It fits well.
I'm glad the color is pretty bright.
Definitely.
I think this might be a must-have!
Tanebo's Fresh Day Cream.
How many times have you used it?
I use it all year round.
Before makeup.
I have a lot of it in my purse.
You can suddenly jump to eye makeup.
This is the one I can't do without.
This one.
Oh, my God!This is bad.
Mr. Pokey before.
I'm really sorry about this.
I've got to use up the last one.
Oh, my God.
I'm so glad.
I'm really worried about my stomach.
Anyway, I'm really protective of my lower eyelids under my eyes.
I always put a lot of pink in my eyeshadow.
It's so bad.
I seriously put it under my eyes every day.
I'm going to make my eyes look like this.
I'm definitely going to expose myself.
I've been feeling a little cute lately.
I'm using it again today.
It's the one I'm wearing.
It's a very limited edition.
It's only sold at Hemisphere Ume in Osaka.
What?
It's so limited!
I'm wearing it today, and it's so luminous.
It's so cute!
Burgundy people will love it.
Is it all eyeshadow?
Or blush?
I put a little bit on top of blush.
And I used it for eyeshadow.
It's so good!
It's really pretty.
I'd like to see the same look in a less blue-ish place.
Oh, I did it!
I love it!
I think our tastes are pretty similar.You and Noru look so much alike.
I know.
The coloring, the lamé.
Even if you mess up your eyeshadow, just put it on.
I'll take care of it.
What about eyebrows?
I'm a lifelong refugee.
It's so hard.
Recently, I liked...
Fujiko's.
Oh, Fujiko.
This is Tassipale No. 05, half-color lame.
And here's the brown.
Eh, it's cute.
Sometimes I do some kind of color.
This beige-ish ivory type lame in the middle here.
If you paint the center of the lamé and then draw with this...
I like that it doesn't look dull.
It's a little bit wax-like.
I've never seen this before.
It's scary.
I don't know.
I'm going to use this lame one for the rest of my life.
The beige kind.
It's like I can get away with changing my hair color or something.
I didn't know there was this much in it.
That's right.
You're a refugee. Your eyebrows.
Yeah, I know.
I'm really into this pink.
Camouflage.
It's so easy to use.
I've also been using eyebrow mascara lately to brighten them up a bit.
Oh, sure.
But Kate...
I've been using Kate brow mascara too.
We're the same.
The same?
BR number two.
BR number 2.
I've been using it my whole life.
I've been using it since I was an idol.
Really?
This is only my first bottle.
It's so good!
And this color is cute, too.
BR5.
It's a little pinkish.
It's pinkish.
I like it so much I have two bottles.
It's so pretty with lame.
I want lame.
Fujiko's Shake Shadow, SV05.
It's called "Tokimeki Greeter.
Wow!
It's uniquely fresh.
You've got it.
It's so dense.
Yes, it is.
Where do you use it?
Under the eyes, on the eyelids, on the inner corner of the eyes, and on the outer corner of the eyes.
Oh, wow.Heh.
I'm imagining this Fujiko with a little more color, like brown or something.
It's just lame.
This is the cutest.
So cute!
I put this on my lips everyday.
Here's a shot of it.
This is soooo good!
Jill's Crystal Bloom Lip Bouquet Serum.
I'm using either #02 or #01 or both.
It's kind of super pigmented.
It's so pretty.
I don't have much in the way of colored glosses.
I'm applying makeup skincare and stuff like that.
First?
Yeah, I put it on when I'm done with my base or before my base.
And my lips went "boom".
Oh, my God, it's so good!
It makes my lips go "boom".
Is this a classic?
It's a classic.
I highly recommend it.
What are you using for lips these days?
Lips... I really like the ones I put out.
But I also use this size for bases and stuff like that.
Peripera?
It's a new one.
I bought it because it looked so good.
But it's kind of...
Cute.
Like this.
It's kind of moist.
It's cute. Yeah.
I like that color.
Dull pink.
But this one today. This one and this one.Let's see. Number 7.
Number 7. Oh, this one's hard.
You don't need the base.
Just mine. You know, maybe you could put it in a bag in your wardrobe.
You can reapply it?
That's right.
That's it for now.
I totally understand.
It gets all dried out in the middle of a concert.
I already made it when I was an idol.
I know, right?
That's what I wanted.
That's what I'm really trying to do.
I don't know about you, but...
Isn't there something there?
It's true.
It's a common practice to paint beautiful idols at encores.
I really like Yuri-San's blush and use it.
Blush.
They introduced it.
A girl who came a lot.
Akari introduced me.
It's an original.
I don't know.
The make-up I gave her last time.
Makeup to make your boyfriend nervous.
I used it to make my boyfriend nervous.
I'm glad.
I don't know if "insecure" is the right word.
Really?
Yeah.
It's kind of cute.
It's cute.
It holds up well. I use it a lot.
It's in my coach.
What kind of color ripper do you use?
I use my own brand of colors.
Lately...
Wait, which one?
Which one? - Oh, wait, Gaultier.
Same thing.
Together.
Minami and Akemi Nakano.
They collaborated.
I found it.
Frogs, right?
Sweets.
Sold out for free.
It's now a product.
It's the same one, but I turned it off.
It's so good.
Isn't it good for TV?
Yeah, it is.
On TV, if you paint it a darker color...
Mouth.
Right?
Here.
It's like a contour.
First of all, you blur it with this.
Once.
That's right.
It was all over the place.
Caracoso with pandé or gel.
With a gel or something.Hold the gels and stuff.
And all the ones I don't have.
Definitely buy them.
Buy it.
I'm so glad I did. You can't go wrong.
This is the best one of all.
This is the best one.
And the hanky.
HANKEW.
I'll find it and buy it.
I really will!
It was a lot of fun.
I knew it.
Talking with people who like tips.
It's really fun.
It's a lot of fun in the dressing room.
Right?
And you too, Akari?
That's right.
On the channel, too.
She turned her head that way and talked.
This way.
Every time.
I'm always on the show.
So please go check it out.
That's all for now.
This is Yuki Kashiwa and Akari Yoshida.
See you soon.
undefined